whatsthewordanswers.org 2014-01-14

# Privacy Policy | What's the Word Answers

Dear visitors of our website! We are glad you are already here. This means either you are looking for answers (you cheating) or you have stumbled across our website and you would like to play the addictive game of whats the word. Our website is updated daily with various levels and answers. You are kindly requested to double check your version of the game because different updates have different level numbers. We would propose you to check the images and try to locate the answers from them. In case you are stuck on a level and you cannot seem to find the solution on our website, drop us a message on our Facebook page (found on the right)

Privacy Policy for www.whatsthewordanswers.org 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@whatsthewordanswers.org. 

At www.whatsthewordanswers.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.whatsthewordanswers.org and how it is used. 

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, www.whatsthewordanswers.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.whatsthewordanswers.org does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.whatsthewordanswers.org.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.whatsthewordanswers.org and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.whatsthewordanswers.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.whatsthewordanswers.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.whatsthewordanswers.org’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
